pinkice.com 2015-12-10

# 

Privacy & Security

### Last Amended October 18, 2013

### Intro

Pink Ice respects customers' Privacy.. The paragraphs below describe our "Privacy Policy." This Privacy Policy applies to the use of the Website (as defined below), including by customers and other persons. Except as otherwise indicated, customers and other persons using the Website are individually and collectively referred to as “you”, “your” or “Customer”, and Pink Ice Inc and its subsidiaries and affiliates are referred to as, "Pink Ice", "we", "us" and "our."

PinkIce.com and any of their affiliated Web pages, are committed to implementing policies and procedures designed to protect your privacy and security, as well as providing our customers the best online shopping experience. In order to make this possible, it is important to understand the types of information we collect from you, how we use this information, shared and safely kept, and how you have the ability to manage its use. In order to offer various products and services to our Customers, Pink Ice collects certain information as described below in this Privacy Policy.

In conjunction with this Privacy Policy, you should also review our [terms](http://dev.pinkice.com/index.php?route=information/information&information_id=5) for a full understanding of the rules governing our Services. [Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html) for information on Internet safety and security from the Federal Trade Commission.

### The Information We Collect From You

Information we collect from you depends on how you use the Website, and the information you may choose to provide to us.

 _Personal Information:_  We may require Customers who visit or use the Website and/or purchase products on the Website to supply us with personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is uniquely identifiable information about you that we collect online, including, but not limited to, your full name, a user name/password, email address, phone number, physical address, financial information, and your credit card information and other billing information. Information in a form that (a) is aggregated with other information, (b) anonymized, or (c) is otherwise is detached, combined, organized, segmented, modified or processed, in each case so as not to be reasonably capable of being associated with you, will not be considered Personal Information, and will not be restricted by this Privacy Policy as to use, sharing or otherwise. Some features of our Services, and certain requested information or products may not be accessible if you choose not to provide us with Personal Information.

If you create an account using your login credentials from a third party service, such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, etc..., we will collect the information that your privacy settings on that third party service allows us to access. We will use this information to create an account for you. This includes collecting the contact information of your friends, if you choose to connect your contacts and address book information with your account, so that you can connect with your friends when you use our Website.  _Automatic Collection of Information:_  Similar to many web properties on the Internet, we automatically track certain information about you as you visit and use our Website to help us create a better shopping experience for you. This tracked or automatically gathered information includes, among other things, your computer’s or device's IP address, browser type, the URLs on the Website you have visited, sections of or content on pages on the Website on which you click, the frequency you visit each page on the Website, what downloads and/or search requests you have made, and time spent on specific pages of the Website.

### Cookies

When you visit our Website, we may drop a small file on your browser called a "cookie". This allows us to make your shopping experience unique to you and ultimately give you a better shopping experience. Depending on the browser you are using, you can turn off "cookies". Please be aware that if you turn off cookies, many functions of our Website will not be available to you, including creating a shopping cart, and making purchases. Moreover, some of our third-party service providers working on our behalf may also utilize their own cookies.

### How We Use Your Information

The personal information you submit to the Website is used to process your order, confirm your order by email, and/or to contact you as necessary regarding your online purchases. We keep your personal information to improve your shopping experience when you return to shop with us. For example, we will save your personal information to maintain your customer account and/or membership to our website so you can log-in to the Website at a later time. Additionally, we keep and may use your personal information to keep track of your purchasing preferences and to help us better understand the types of products and services you are interested in. We will use your e-mail and mailing address to send information about upcoming sales, arrival of new products, contests, and promotions. If you decide to participate in one of our contests or promotions, we may use your personal information to send you e-mails about our products, contests and promotions. If you do not wish to receive our weekly email newsletter, you may unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.

### How Your Personal Information Is Safe

Whenever Personal Information is stored on our computers, time in which depends on factors, that information is protected from unauthorized access or use by way of passwords or other industry-acknowledged means. Additionally, our servers are firewall protected. We take extra caution in keeping your personal information safe and secure. Any transmission of sensitive material, such as credit card information, will only take place under secure connections. We appreciate your help in safeguarding the integrity of your own and others' privacy. We hope you will use common rationale whenever you disclose Personal Information over the Internet. Just as importantly, we encourage you to let us know immediately if you suspect that Personal Information you share with us is being used in any way contrary to this Privacy Policy. Lastly, 100% secure data transmission or storage does not exist, so we cannot guarantee complete security of your Personal Information. Please contact us if you have knowledge of any illegal activity.

 _Promotions and Marketing:_

Unless you choose not to hear from us, if you provide your email address to us (whether on the Website or on a third party Web site) for any reason, we may use this to contact you for promotional or other purposes. You can opt out at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of every promotional email or, you can give us call and we will unsubscribe you manually. Please know that despite unsubscribing from our email promotional emails, Pink Ice may still contact you regarding your order(s), purchase(s) or any issues relating any business you conduct with Pink Ice. In some instances, the Website may run friend referral promotions in which we will obtain and use his/her referred email address for promotional purposes.

 _Merger or Acquisition_

As Pink Ice continues to grow and adapt, we may choose to buy or sell some of our business or related assets. In doing so, Personal Information and other information we collect from you will generally be transferred as well.

### Pink Ice is Not Intended for Children

Our Website are for general audience and is not intended for children under age 13. Pink Ice does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under age 13, and if you are under the age of 13 you should not register or provide information on our Website. If you have knowledge that a child under the age of 13 has submitted Personal Information to us, please email give us a call at (877)494-1288.

### Effective Date and Right to Modify

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date first written above the first paragraph. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If any material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, Pink Ice will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. _ANY ACCESS OR USE OF THE WEBSITE BY YOU PRIOR TO ANY CHANGES SHALL CONSTITUTE AND BE DEEMED YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY._  If you do not want to be bound by this Privacy Policy, do not use or access any part of the Website.

### Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy.

PinkIce.com  
Customer Service  
1458 S. San Pedro St #304  
Los Angeles, Ca 90015  
Mon-Fri 9AM-6PM PST  
Toll Free: (877)494-1288  
International: (213)745-8717
